(Bert:)You just don't want
to go out with me
(Bert:)because I have
an off-putting personality.
(Amy:)No, that's not true.
(Amy:)My boyfriend has
an off-putting personality, too.
(Amy:)Way worse than you.
(Bert:)Don't worry. I'm used to it.
(Bert:)I mean, I'm big and weird
and funny-looking
(Bert:)and no one ever wants
to do anything with me.
(Amy:)Don't say that.
(Bert:)It's okay.
I know I'm a monster.
(Amy:)No, Bert, come on.
(Amy:)I'd love to go to the
mineral show with you.
(Bert:)Sweet. It's a date.
(Stuart:)-No, it's not.
Too late!
I (ALTERNATIVE MUSIC PLAYS) I
(Leonard:)Wow.
(Stuart:)Yeah. Haven't seen this
many people in my store
(Stuart:)since that Korean church bus
crashed through my front window.
-Hey! Stuart!
-Jesse.